Guide to the Henry H. Jones Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Henry H. Jones papers
1965-1996
SC0859
Jones, Henry H.
8.75 Linear feet
Collection contains his professional papers pertaining to his teaching and research, including syllabi and other class materials, notes, lectures, correspondence, articles, and illustrations; the research files pertain to the skeletal system. There are also several files pertaining to Physicians for Social Responsibility.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
Professor Emeritus of radiology, Stanford School of Medicine. Jones earned his BA in chemistry at Haverford College in 1939 and his MD from Yale. After several years as an instructor at the Army School of Roentgenology, he joined the faculty at the Stanford School of Medicine in 1948 and taught until his retirement in 2006. Jones was a founding member of Physicians for Social Responsibility.
Description of the Collection
Collection contains his professional papers pertaining to his teaching and research, including syllabi and other class materials, notes, lectures, correspondence, articles, and illustrations; the research files pertain to the skeletal system. There are also several files pertaining to Physicians for Social Responsibility.
Access Terms
Jones, Henry H.; Stanford University. School of Medicine--Faculty.; Radiology, Medical.
Collection Contents
- Papers, Accession ARCH-2007-052
  - Sartoris Questionnaires (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Topics (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hyperparathyroidism Slides etc., for Ortho. Conference (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Neurofibromatosis Radiology Ortho. Conference (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Orthopedics-Radiology Case of the Month (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dept. of Radiology Bone Conference (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bone Conference, 1980, 1981, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bone Conference, May 14, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bone Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dave Sartoris Conference Quiz and Answers (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Spine Talk (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Back Pain Lecture Notes, etc. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Skeletal Changes in Hematological Diseases, February 23, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arthritis [Reprints] (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arthritis Lecture to Residents, March 4, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - The Arthritic Hand-Talk to Arthritis Group-June 21, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arthritis Lecture #1 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arthritis Lecture #2 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Technique-Efficacy Studies (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Technique-Radiation Dosage, Exposure, etc. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Technique-Soft Tissues (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Technique-Skeletal (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Radiographic Technique-Upper Extremity (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Radiographic Technique-Lower Extremity (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Technique-Cervical Spine (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Technique-Sacroiliac Joint (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Technique-Head (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Technique-Neck (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Technique-Chest (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Technique-Abdomen (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Radiology Department-Organization, Management (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arthritis in Black and White (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Computerization of Pathology Bone Tumor File (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Teardrop Project-Pelvis (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Osteoarthritis of the Hand-A Comparison of Handedness and Hand Use (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Resnick-Arthrography of Wrist Lecture, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 216 Hand, Cases, Correspondence, References, etc. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Historical Collection (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Orthopedic Division-CPC Cases Wed. AM Conference (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Slide Collections (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Radiology-Orthopedic Conferences-Gauchers Disease; Coccidioidomycosis (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lectures to Residents-Paget's Diesaese, Dec. 5-9, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Talks to Radiology Residents, April 24-26, 1984 with Jon Ross (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Films-to be copied (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Material etc. for Presentation to Committee Academic and Achievement to get one unit academic credit for Radiology #237 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Advertising for DRNM Course #237, February 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - PSR [Physicians for Social Responsibility] Fundraising (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Old handouts-Can Be Updated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Spare Copies of Handouts (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sign up Slips, Medical Students, February 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Handout Package for DRNM Course #237, February 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Signup Slips, Nurses and MDs, February 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence-DRNM course #237, February 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Handouts for DRNM Course #237 (masters), February 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - CME Credit Masters Form and Blank Paper (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - CME Credit for DRNM Course #237, February 3, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Handouts for DRNM Course #237, February 21, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Signup for SRNM Course #237, February 2, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Evaluations, February 2, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Handout Contents, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Advertising, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Student Course Evaluations, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Loose materials (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Jones' References (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Melanotic Progonoma (with slides) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hypertrophic Osteoarthropathy (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - PSR (Physicians for social responsibility)-Current (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Letters to Kennedy and Korn re: housing for PSR (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - PSR Course on Effects of Nuclear War-Current Material, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility Event Surveys (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Jules Riskin Project-Family Interaction and Nuclear War (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - The Physician and Nuclear Age-Course #237 (References), February 6, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Advertising, February 4, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Copy of Handout Package #237, February 4, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - CME Credit for PSR National Meeting, March 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - H.L.A. Fundraising Letters for PSR (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Signup Slips, House Staff (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - CME Credit-Radiology #237, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CME Credit-Master Form and Stationary-DRNM #237, February 2, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Masters for Radiology #237 Handouts, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dr #237, April 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Radiology #237-Expenses, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Evaluation Sheets-Radiology #237, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Grades for Radiology #237, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Radiology #237-Contents of Handout Lists (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Radiology #237-Copies of Articles Removed from Prior Handouts (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Handouts, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Modern Warfare- Nuclear, Chemical, Biological-Handouts (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Radiology #237-Advertising, April 11, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Melanotic Progonoma of Calvaria-Updated, August 7, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Pragonoma Saper-Statistics Listings (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Pragonoma Illustrations-Negatives (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pragonoma Illustrations (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Melanotic Progonoma-Medline Search, etc. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Organic Culture-Technician Applications (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Organic Culture-References (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Organic Culture-Material (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Simone Bishop-Calame (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Organic Culture-Ideas and Projects (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Request for Supplementary Part I Funds (file with l22d5) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Research Funding (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Culture Room Plans (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Organic Culture (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Experimental-Tissue Culture-Organ Culture-Animal Observation (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - MRI Studies Knee- Jogging Project 1989 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jogging Project- Knee Results Sheet –folder 1 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jogging Project- Knee Results Sheet –folder 2 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Jogging Project- Knee Results Sheet –folder 3 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jogging Project- Knees-Re-dos (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Positioning Articles- re: knee exams (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Blank Forms -Knees (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Jogging Project –Spine-1987 evaluation subjects- folder 1 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jogging Project –Spine-1987 evaluation subjects- folder 2 of 3 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jogging Project –Spine-1987 evaluation subjects- folder 3 of 3 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - OA study (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Jogging-Hand Results Sheet- copy 1 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - B Knee form Henry (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - B-Spine 1 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - A-Spine 1 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - A-Spine 2 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - B-Spine 2 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - CT Bone Density-Graph Paper (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Written- Published Articles Re: Jogging Project (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Unlabeled (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Duplicate of Jogging Package Provided by Dr. Bjorkengren (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Jogging Project- Costs and Planning for 1989 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Information for QCT [quantitative computed tomography] – Jogging Project- Jones copy-1989 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - B-Film Spine (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - QCT [quantitative computed tomography] References from RSNA meeting (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Spine Densitometry- CT (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Jogging Project- References Relating to Manuscript (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Unlabeled (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Bone Densitometry- Syntex Study (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Elbow Project – Chicago Exhibit-AMA (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Elbow Project – RSNA Exhibit (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tennis Project – Computer Instructions Etc (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Elbow Project – Misc Notes, Ideas, Etc (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Carol Chin – Original Data (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Fat Layer Calculations (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Notes from Statistics Course – B. Brown (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Humeral Hypertrophy in Response to Exercise (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Tennis Elbow – Plans for Palm Springs (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Elbow Project – Data Correction and Verification – Douglas (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Elbow Project – Means plus/minus 2 S.D. per Douglas Jones (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Elbow Project Material (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Paper Sent to Journal of Sports Medicine (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Elbow Project – RSNA Exhibit – Misc Worksheets + Data from Exhibits + Papers (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Elbow Project Folder #2 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Elbow Project – Grant Applic. – Presentation Applic. – Exhibit Applic. Etc. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Elbow Project – Instructions for Writing for J.B.J.S. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Unlabeled (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Elbow Project – Slides (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Elbow Project – Technique (G-39) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Humeral Hypertrophy Paper (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Elbow Project – Protocol for X-ray Measurements (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Elbow Project – Comparison AP vs lat diameters of Humerus at item level (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Elbow Project – Carol Chin Data Copy 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Players Etc (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - US Income Tax (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Tennis Project (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Carol Chin Data (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Elbow Project – Recalculation Parameters from Raw X-Ray Data of J. Priest – Per Doug Jones – Folder 1 of 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Banff Talk – Copies of Our Papers (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Phone Numbers (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Tuesday Seminar Notes (1/3) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Tuesday Seminar Notes (2/3) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Tuesday Seminar Notes (3/3) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - AUR ‘98 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Memos – Teaching File (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - International Skeletal Society 24th Annual Refresher Course (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Slide Collections + Tape Cassettes (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Radiology #237 Correspondence ‘96 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Radiology #237 Eval. Sheets, 11 Feb ‘95 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Radiology #237 Correspondence ‘95 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Radiology #237 Program 11 Feb ‘95 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Radiology #237 Sign In Form - Course 11 Feb ‘95 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Radiology #237 Advertisements 11 Feb ‘95 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Radiology #237 Programs (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Radiology #237 Advertisements 11 Feb ‘95 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Radiology #237 Seminars 11 Feb ‘95 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Stanford PSR Annual Meeting 10 Dec ‘95 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Radiology #237 11 Feb. ‘95 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Radiology 237 Copies of Handout 10 Feb. ‘96 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Radiology 237 10 Feb. '96 List of Handouts (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Radiology 237 Dr. Larry Koran 10 Feb ‘96 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Radiology 237 Maps 11 Feb. ‘95 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Radiology 237 10 Feb. '96 Sign-in Forms (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Radiology 237 10 Feb. '96 Essays (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Radiology #237 Seminars 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Radiology 237 10 Feb. '96 Evaluation Sheets (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Stress Fractures – Lecture Notes (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - #237 5 Feb. 1994 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - #237 5 Feb. 1994 Program (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Radiology #237 5 Feb 1994 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence – Radiology #237 1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Victor Sidel (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - #237 Advertisements (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Direction Signs for Seminars Radiology #237 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - #237 5 Feb '94 Evaluation Sheets (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - #237 – 5 Feb '94 Completed Evaluation Sheets (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Totally Hip, Vol. 1 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Totally Hip, Vol. 2 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Totally Hip, Vol. 3 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Radiology Clerkship – Content etc. of Bone Lectures (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Department Brochures '76 (Blue), '87 Phys. Referral Kit (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Dept. Rad. Policy Matters Historical (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Reports on Department of Radiology Annual Report, etc. (Historical) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Stanford University School of Medicine Old (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Professional – Misc, (Vita, etc.) (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Awards (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - CME Materials (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Certification – X-Ray Operator + Accreditation Material etc. B2a (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - License etc. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Henry H. Jones, MD [includes 3.5" floppy disk] (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Photos – dept various years – unmarked (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Radiology of Skeletal Trauma/Syllabus (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Department Schedules and Rotations (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - 1) Ankle therapies per cases 48-56; 2) Experimental + Diagnostic Techniques; 3) Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - References (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Radiology of Skeletal Trauma/Syllabus (incomplete) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Elbow Project – Illustration, Experiments, etc (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Elbow Project – Exhibit – Dallas, Texas (Detail Studies) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Elbow Project – Recalculation of Raw X-Ray Data – Folder 2 of 4 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Elbow Project – Recalculation of Raw X-Ray Data – Folder 3 of 4 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Elbow Project – Recalculation of Raw X-Ray Data – Folder 4 of 4 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Cutoffs – Garbage (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Elbow Project – Ultrasound (G-39) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Elbow Project – Magnification – Spare Copies (G-39) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Elbow Project – Forms (G-39) (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Table I – Douglas Jones Calculations (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Final Correction Copy (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Copy for Doctor Nagel (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Table I (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Gallery Proofs – JB and JS Article (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Elbow Project – References and Reprints (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Data for Comparison, Published Data, Normal Published Values (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Table II – Intermediate Form And Info (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Elbow Project – Cross Section Humeri (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Elbow Project – Requests for Reprints – Sports Medicine Article (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Elbow Project – Orthopedics Digest Paper (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Elbow Project – Dallas Talk (G-39) (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - American College of Ortho. Sung. Bone Course Notes, 1974 Dallas (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tracings – Elbows (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Elbow Project – Changes and Rotation (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Elbow Project – Magnification and Rotation Writeups (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper - Fig. 2 With Legend (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper - Fig. 2 With Legend (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper Xerox Copies - Fig. 1 and Fig. 4 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper - Fig. 3 With Legend (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Fig. 4 With Legend (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Medical Illustration (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Current Corrected Version (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Elbow Project – Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Fig. 1 With Legend (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Humeral Hypertrophy Paper – Corrections Copy (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Unlabeled (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Humerus Article – Revised Version (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Humerus Article – Original Version (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Elbow Project – Computer Programs Available (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Elbow Project (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Elbow Project – Statistical Formulas Used (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Elbow Project – Computer Runs by Rich Guisti (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Elbow Project – List of Computer Runs (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Elbow Project – Cartoons (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Elbow Project – Comparison Priest vs Jones Measurements (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Elbow Project – Reprints Chin + Priest et al (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Elbow Project – RSNA Exhibit - Precis (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Elbow Project – RSNA Exhibit (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Elbow Project – Work In Progress Report (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Elbow Project RSNA Exhibit – Tape Slide Manuscript (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Comparison of Means, Differences, Std. Devs, & P. Values; Whole Group vs. No Rotational Difference (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Elbow Project – Vanguard Measurements of Cadaver Arm and Calculations of Effects of Rotation – Spare Copy (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Elbow Project – Vanguard Measurements of Cadaver Arm and Rotation Calculations (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Elbow Project – Magnification – Folder 2 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Loose Materials (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - The Elbow and Tennis – A Study of Expert Players [Cassette] (Box 14)
  - Radiological Tables and Circular Slide Rule (Box 14)
  - The Elbow and Tennis – A Study of Expert Players [Film Roll] (Box 14)
  - Restricted Material:
    - Bone Pathology Collection (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Lanier Notes, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Lanier Notes, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Lanier Notes, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Lanier Notes, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Potential Cases for Department Bone-ER Conference (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Teaching Files (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Teaching Files (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Teaching Cases (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Teaching Lists, etc. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Teaching Files (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Cases for Teaching or Special Interest (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Teaching Cases, August 1981 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Teaching Courses, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Teaching Cases, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Teaching Cases, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Teaching Cases, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Teaching Cases, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Teaching Cases, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Teaching Cases, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - TF [teaching files] Listings (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Teaching Cases (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Teaching Cases (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - For Teaching (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Teaching Cases and References (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Teaching Cases to Check (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bone and Joint Cases Shown at Department Conference (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bone Conference, April 3, 1980-May 14, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Bone Conference (spurs of spine), September 30, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Bone Conference (assorted arthritis cases, various areas), November 6, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Bone Conference (Ankylosing Spondylitis), December 1, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Bone Conference (Feet), January 5, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Bone Conference, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Bone Conference, January 17, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Bone Conference (Pelvis and Sacrum), January 2, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Cases Shown at Howard Steinbach Conferences (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Back Pain-List of Cases and Slides (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Set Clinic (Delayed Rupture of Spleen 1976), February 26, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Talk to Radiation Oncologists and Therapists on Detection of Metastases (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Rheumatology Conferences, 1980, 1981, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Classic Tumor and Related Examples-"Board Review" Conference, April 30, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Paget's Disease- Selected References (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Orthopedic Pathology Course (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Teaching Cases, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Teaching Cases, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Extra-Osseous Ewing's Paper (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - DRNM Course #237 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Student Groups for SRNM #237, February 3, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Kris Hartman-Case Reports (periosteal reaction in pt. E ulcerative colitis) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - PSY 237 Physicians' Role in the Nuclear Age, February 8, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - The Physician and Nuclear Weapons Course, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - The Physician and Nuclear Weapons Course, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Radiology #237-Student Signups, February 4, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Signups for Radiology #237, April 11, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Teaching Files, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Teaching Files, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Teaching Files, 1965-1966 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jogging Project- Knees-1986 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - OA Study/ Hands (1) (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - OA Study/ Hands (2) (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Jogging Project-Spine-1986 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Jogging Project- Combined Cortical Thickness (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Jogging Project-Hands 1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Spine CT-Assorted Forms-Spares (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Jogging Project- CT 1986 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Spine CT- Detailed Image Observation (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Jogging Stress- CT Bone Densitometry- Patient Results (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Jogging Project- Manuscript (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Loose Materials (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Elbow Project – Dr. James Priest -> Raw Data (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Elbow Project (G-39) (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Stress Fractures – Cases Pulled (1/2) (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Stress Fractures – Cases Pulled (2/2) (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Signups for Radiology #237 10 Feb. ‘96 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Information for QCT Jogging Project-Dr. Feller's Copy, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Radiology #237 11 Feb. '95 Grading (Box 19, Folder 1)